hello to pitch yourself I'm black out
مرحبًا بملعب نفسك أنا أسود
and out the build a roller coaster at
والخروج من السفينة الدوارة في
Kobayashi your ground isn't a vehicle
كوباياشي الأرض ليست سيارة
ever showing you how to build up going a
من أي وقت مضى تظهر لك كيفية بناء الذهاب
world goes to that folder by yourself
العالم يذهب إلى هذا المجلد من قبل نفسك
who did it record lady's house hey this
من فعل ذلك سجل منزل سيدة يا هذا
is the inside this is the pod ladies
هو داخل هذا السيدات جراب
t-rex I can't go inside it and and no
تي ريكس لا أستطيع الذهاب داخله و لا
one died be showing you how to burger by
توفي واحد يظهر لك كيف برجر من قبل
itself water coaster
نفسها السفينة المياه
I don't want timer by you buddy
أنا لا أريد جهاز توقيت من قبل صديق لك
largest car here is a river is it well
أكبر سيارة هنا هي النهر هو على ما يرام
my kids but I don't and this is my
أطفالي ولكني لا أفعل هذا
rendition bumblebees making smoke
نقل النحل صنع الدخان
and bite you right in the water
و عضك في الماء
so let me show you my restaurant I built
لذا دعني أريك مطعمي الذي قمت ببنائه
No
لا
now if you want to call my Western 1/2
الآن إذا كنت تريد الاتصال بي الغربي 1/2
and then go down the hall there's me 15
ثم اذهب الى القاعة هناك 15
Empire joy
الفرح الإمبراطوري
oh you're precious so first you push
أه أنت ثمينة أولاً تدفع
down will cook it then you do this I'm
سوف طهي ثم قمت بذلك أنا
Douglas which to power it up the goal
دوغلاس لتزويدها بالهدف
you have to find those letters so if you
عليك ان تجد تلك الحروف حتى لو كنت
want a lever swish oh but not the door
تريد رافعة حفيف يا ولكن ليس الباب
oh I didn't know that was Julius are
يا لم أكن أعرف أن كان يوليوس ل
let's place it on top floor till - I
دعونا نضعها في الطابق العلوي حتى - أنا
make this um I rather go to buy a shelf
جعل هذا أم أذهب بدلا من شراء الرف
then you keep placing it and then you do
ثم تستمر في وضعها ومن ثم تفعل
this this this and this but not that ah
هذا هذا هذا وهذا هذا ولكن ليس هذا آه
this and push the lever and the lever
هذا ودفع رافعة والرافعة
it'll make turn on but and you're down
سوف يتحول لكنك وأنت في الأسفل
there we'll go with that
هناك سنذهب مع ذلك
it keeps dirtiness brings back don't
انها تبقي القذارة يعيد لا
make all of this um then go you're all
جعل كل هذا ثم اذهب أنت كل شيء
of your dope part I found under straw
من مخدر جزء وجدت تحت القش
I think more time wanted to help me
أعتقد أن المزيد من الوقت أراد مساعدتي
in distress tell me now
في الضيق قل لي الآن
I'm dad first a user a turn donkeys land
أنا أب لأول مرة المستخدم أرض حمير بدوره
I say yeah yeah how it goes
اقول نعم نعم كيف تسير الامور
yeah yeah I met don't get them if you
نعم نعم التقيت لا تحصل عليها إذا كنت
want to forget push lift and it also
نريد أن ننسى رفع الضغط وأيضا
pushed all right and push the brake
دفعت كل الحق ودفع الفرامل
button right here
زر هنا
now firstly and ever and a house now
الآن أولا وقبل كل شيء وبيت الآن
this will help patients help for it
هذا سوف يساعد المرضى على المساعدة لذلك
helped how high you want it to be
ساعد مدى ارتفاع كنت تريد أن تكون
what I noticed actually didn't want the
ما لاحظته في الواقع لم أكن أريد
towel yet tennis remove captain area
منشفة بعد التنس إزالة منطقة القبطان
he's over there just trying to arrange
هو هناك فقط يحاول الترتيب
party
حفل
here - the protection area so I can't
هنا - منطقة الحماية بحيث لا أستطيع
build air so
بناء الهواء حتى
and my one dish here don't play son
ولدي طبق واحد هنا لا تلعب ابنه
don't throw stress making that and
لا رمي الإجهاد يجعل ذلك و
something that's weird
شيء غريب
now and I'll show you how this suture
الآن وسوف أعرض لكم كيف هذا الخيط
train goes and the wall coaster out once
يذهب القطار والحائط السفينة مرة واحدة
you were on here and I fell down and
كنت هنا وأنا سقطت و
died and got hurt so their place won't
توفي وتضررت حتى مكانهم لن
go down
انزل
very happy showing more timers sock-doc
سعيد جدا تظهر المزيد من الموقتات جورب دوك
older wiser Babycham free free
كبار السن الأكثر حكمة Babycham مجانا
you can have big successes
يمكنك الحصول على نجاحات كبيرة
thank you for watching goodbye learned
شكرا لك على مشاهدة وداعا تعلمت
out half a second ransom hot sauce a
خارج نصف صلصة فدية ساخنة نصف أ
face inside
وجه الداخل